careersidekick.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy • Career Sidekick

_Last modified: May 17, 2018_

CareerSidekick.com is committed to ensuring your privacy is protected.

This document outlines our privacy guidelines, to which you agree by navigating this site. Regular updates of the privacy policy are completed, requiring you to check back on this policy from time to time.

### What Information Do We Collect?

**Personal Data.** Personal Data is information that identifies a particular individual. In order for us to provide service to you, we may collect the following Personal Data from you:

  * Your first and last name
  * Your email address

We collect this information from you when you subscribe to our email newsletter, order one of our products, or fill out a form on our website.

If you leave a comment on the website, we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**Other Data.** When you visit our website, we want to make it easy, useful and reliable. To do this, we also collect other information which does *not* identify you. We do this in the following ways/methods:

  * Google Analytics
  * Server Logs

More information on each can be found below:

**Google Analytics.** Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are small text files placed on your computer, to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form – no personally identifiable information is collected about you unless you explicitly submit that information to us. Google Analytics is a free tool that lets us see what’s going on with our website traffic, where our visitors are coming from and what are they doing on our website. Most web browsers allow you to turn off cookies. To do this look at the “help” menu on your browser. Switching off cookies may restrict the use of the Service and/or delay or affect the way in which it operates.

**Server logs.** We use server log information for purposes such as calculating site usage levels, helping diagnose problems with CareerSidekick’s servers and administering CareerSidekick.com. These server logs may include information such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, host name, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, the time(s) of your visit(s) and the web page(s) that you visited. Collecting IP addresses is standard practice on the Internet and is done automatically by many web sites.

### What Do We Do With This Information?

Any of the information we collect may be used in the following ways:

  * To improve our website and user experience.
  * To respond to your customer service requests and inquiries.
  * To process transactions and fulfill our obligation to you when you order a product or request information from us.
  * To send periodic emails- the email address you provide may be used to send you information about relevant products and services. You can change your mind later with regard to receiving emails from us by contacting us at any time. We also include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email we send.

### How Do We Keep Your Personal Data Safe?

In order to keep your Personal Data and all the other information we have stored safe, we have implemented various security measures and taken reasonable steps to prevent unauthorized access, use, alteration, destruction or disclosure of your Personal Data.

Your Personal Data will be stored in a secure environment and treated confidentially. We will, however, use a hosting provider to store data, including Personal Data. The hosting provider may not use your Personal Data for any other purposes besides storing it, and we require the hosting provider to act consistently with this Privacy Policy and to use appropriate security measures to protect your Personal Data.

We will take all reasonable precautions to ensure that our staff and employees who have been specifically granted access to information about you have received adequate training to ensure that they process that information only in accordance with this policy and with our obligations under applicable legislations.

### Do We Disclose Any Personal Data to Outside Parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties, with exception to third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, after confirming these parties agree to keep this information confidential.

We may, however, release personal information when required to do so by law enforcement, or in cases where it’s necessary in order to comply with the law.

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

We make every effort possible to only use data processors and third party companies that are compliant with GDPR and other international privacy regulations.

### How Long We Retain Your Data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

If you order one of our products, the transaction log is also retained indefinitely. This is so we can provide customer support and verify that you did indeed purchase said product if any customer support issues or questions arise in the future.

If you provide your email address on our website, the details you submit are retained indefinitely so we can continue to provide service and information. We will refresh consent every 2 years to ensure we still have your permission to email you.

Google Analytics user and event data is retained for 50 months from the last visit.

### Information Collected Automatically

Career Sidekick automatically collects your IP address and referring website address, browser type, domain name and website access frequency. This information is intended to help improve your online experience on our site. Career Sidekick uses cookies to track usage patterns on the site and to control the display of content, as well as to offer other functionalities. You can turn off cookies in your web browser’s settings at any time.

For more information on cookies, see below:

### Cookies

Your web browser offers so-called “cookies” which, if you allow their use, store small amounts of data on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies do not contain any Personal Information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify you personally. However, cookies assist us in tracking which of our features you like best. Therefore, cookies enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser settings. Our site is viewable even if you disable the cookie function in your browser.

### Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Embedded Content From Other Websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed at people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### What Rights You Have Over Your Data

If you’ve signed up for an email newsletter, left a comment on our site, or ordered a product from us, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us.

You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Contact

Should you wish to review the Personal Data being held by us about you, you can contact us at [this page](https://careersidekick.com/contact), or make a request in writing to the following address:

Biron Clark, 1530 P B Lane # C4719, Wichita Falls, Texas, 76302

Should you wish for us to permanently delete your Personal Data held by us, we will do so upon your request. In such cases, you understand that we will not be able to provide service or support to you in the future.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may occasionally make changes to this Privacy Policy. If we do, we will update the “Last Modified” date above.
